https://caritasfamilysolutions.org/privacy-policy/

Locations
Internet Privacy PolicyCaritas Family Solutions Internet Privacy PolicyOverviewCaritas Family Solutions will respect the privacy of our online visitors. We may collect information on or through this site that can personally identify you only when it is voluntarily offered by you. For example, we collect personally identifiable information to respond to visitor questions and comments about us, our services, or donations made through this site, and any additional updates.What Information Do We Collect?Caritas Family Solutions collects two types of information: personal voluntary registration information, such as name, address, phone number, and e-mail address, and non-personal statistical information, such as site traffic and usage patterns.How Do We Use It?This information is used primarily to encourage donations from people interested in supporting the agency’s human services programs; to provide information about our mission and accomplishments to our donors; and to improve the design and structure of our website. It is used solely by Caritas Family Solutions and others involved in the operation of this website and will never be sold or given to third parties.SecurityAll financial transactions on this website are processed in a secure format. E-mail submissions of personal data for specific requests of information is neither shared nor solicited with any source. Caritas Family Solutions is committed to protecting your privacy while you use this website and uses industry-proven standards and technologies, including a firewall system to protect that information. Please submit any questions, comments or suggestions you may have by the means listed below.Terms Of UseThe text materials contained on our site may be used, downloaded, reproduced or reprinted, provided that appropriate acknowledgment appears in all copies and provided that such use, download, reproduction or reprint is for non-commercial or personal use only. The text materials contained in this Web site may not be modified in any way. All rights in photographs, illustrations, artworks, and other graphic materials are reserved to Christian Social Services of Illinois and/or the copyright owners. Prior permission to use, reproduce, or reprint any photograph, illustration, artwork, or other graphic material must be obtained from the copyright owner, regardless of the intended use.At Caritas Family Solutions our goal is to serve the community. We honor and respect your privacy. Caritas Family Solutions does not share your name and/or your address with anyone. We do not sell address lists. When you make a donation to Caritas Family Solutions you can be sure that we do not give out any information about you to public or private sources.To those who seek our services, we maintain your information within strict guidelines of confidentiality. You may request changes and/or removal of any and all information we have received from you using the following means listed below. If you have any questions about Caritas Family Solutions policies and procedures, please contact:Kelly LeChienDirector of Quality ImprovementCaritas Family Solutions8601 West Main Street, Suite 201Belleville, IL 62223-1719618-213-8712 (desk)877-722-2748 (toll free)618-213-8777(fax)Kelly.LeChien@caritasfamily.orgChanges In PolicyCaritas Family Solutions reserves the right to change its Internet Privacy Policy based upon the needs of the agency.Direct MarketingPersonally identifiable information or prospect information may at some future opportunity be used to market back to the subject of that information. Individuals may at any time opt-out of our marketing program.If you would prefer not to receive e-mail updates from Caritas Family Solutions or if you would like to change your email preferences, simply click here.
Contact Us
Join Mailing List
Locations
Employment Opportunities
Privacy PolicyOur Commitment to Quality
St. John Bosco Children’s Center is licensed as a Child Care Institution by the Illinois Department of Children & Family Services License #180025. Caritas Family Solutions is licensed as a Child Welfare Agency by the Illinois Department of Children & Family Services License #003976. Caritas Family Solutions is licensed as a CILA Service Provider by the Illinois Department of Human Services License #201300016S.Caritas Family Solutions is a 501(c)(3) organization and donations are tax deductible as allowed by law. EIN #37-0661500.
Facebook
Instagram
Linkedin
Twitter
Youtube
